[Nora]
This is a joint initiative with the NYPD.
Alice Black and Frank Choi
will be running point from the bureau.
Detective Daniel Kelly is the lead
on the Caleb Easton homicide.
and Detective Marshall Connelly
for Oliver Charles.
Who's the teenager
sitting on Jay Easton's lap?
[Alice] I ran the face through
Child Protective Services.
and there's a match.
Isabel Luna.
-I think it's her.
-Well done.
[Alice]
And there's one more person.
That girl...
that's her.
-This is who we're looking for.
-[Frank] We don't know that.
[Alice]
This girl's wearing the same dress
that the suspect is wearing
in the bodega.
-I think it's a distraction.
-A distraction?
[Frank]
We're doing what she wants us to do.
We're... we're asking questions about
Jay Easton instead of going after her.
Did Caleb suffer?
Can you think of any reason
she'd be targeting him?
-No.
-Do you know if he was ever arrested
for solicitation of an underage girl?
Speak to our family lawyer.
[Danny] These guys
I've been working with for years.
they don't fucking talk to me anymore.
But here's the crazy shit.
You don't fucking
talk to me anymore either.
[Catherine]
I could really use a place to stay.
Yeah.
[Blanchard]
Marta. I wanna finally meet you.
So. let me take you out
for some light bites.
Hi.
-What happened with you and Danny?
-[car door slams]
[Alice] Go back in the house.
[dogs barking in distance]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Alice breathing deeply]
[line ringing]
-[phone ringing]
-[sports playing on TV]
[phone stops ringing]
[♪ somber music playing]
[voice]
Your call has been forwarded
-to an automatic voice message system.
-[sighs]
-2-1-2.
-[phone clicks]
[sighs]
Hey. guys.
Liam should probably
get to bed now.
Yeah.
[Liam laughing]
They actually told me
you're a little late
on your copay this month.
Yeah. we're just. um. still sorting out
-all the new billing with the divorce.
-Yeah.
You know. if you ever decide to take him
outta here. I work for cash off hours.
I got others who will. too.
They didn't tell you I was a cop?
Oh.
Oh. hey. it's fine.
I love you.
[Liam vocalizes]
[Catherine]
How could buses be free?
Well. it's like a virtuous cycle
instead of a vicious cycle. you know?
So. it's like. if buses are free.
then ridership goes up.
which decreases traffic.
which increases bus speed.
which. you know.
increases ridership. right?
Are you sure you don't want
-any of these muscles?
-Yeah.
I... well. I know it's like a weird thing
to get a tinned fish on a first date.
but like. I just fucking love tinned fi...
Is this a first date?
I know we haven't. like.
defined it or anything yet.
but. um. honestly. I have been
celibate for an entire year
just 'cause I was so tired
of dating around my friend circle.
I date guys as well but. like.
everybody went to an Ivy...
-Mm.
-and everybody fucking hated it.
and blah. blah. blah. blah. blah.
So. needless to say. I was really glad
when you slid into my DMs. if you will.
Obviously. because you're hot.
But also 'cause I'm like.
I'm just really interested
in the work you do.
You know. like your advocacy
as a former sex worker.
-Yeah.
-Mm.
So. Marta. if you're comfortable...
would you mind telling me...
like. what was it like?
It made me really angry.
Wow.
Oh. my God. you're so brave.
So. tell me about your family.
Yeah. um. it's the three of us.
-Mm.
-You know.
We're really close.
which is really nice.
-[chuckles]
-And you live with your parents?
Yeah. did I tell you that?
I saw it on your feed.
-My fucking feed.
-[chuckles]
Oh. my God. I have to unplug.
Yeah.
[breathing heavily]
[Cole] Hey. I thought you said
that you were married.
I am. yeah.
[chuckles] Yeah.
-[laughing] Okay.
-He's away.
-Uh-huh.
-He has really. uh...
-[Cole sighs]
-big...
-[Cole laughing]
-muscles.
He could kill you.
-Oh yeah?
-Yeah. he could just...
[chuckles]
Have you ever seen anyone
after they've been shot?
It's so gross.
Oh. you're fucked up.
Yeah.
[whispering]
What would you do if I hurt you?
[grunting]
-[♪ mellow percussive music playing]
-[exhales sharply]
[Blanchard]
Fuck. Oh. fuck. yeah.
Oh. my fucking God.
Oh. my God!
Oh! Oh. fuck. yeah.
you hot. fucking slut.
Oh. you slut. Fuck!
Oh shit. fuck.
[chuckles]
Hey. what?
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
you okay?
Yeah.
It's just that word.
[Blanchard]
What. "slut"?
Yeah.
Oh. my God. oh. my God.
oh. my God. oh. my God. I'm so sorry.
I don't know what my problem is.
I. like. I... I can't cum
unless I talk like that. so. like. oh. I...
fuck. I feel like such a fucking fraud.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so. so sorry.
Can you... can you. can you forgive me?
Please?
Could you just hold me?
Yeah.
Yeah. yeah. of course.
Yeah. I love a cuddle.
Yeah. Yeah.
[sighs] Oh.
[soft kiss]
[whispering] By the way.
do you mind leaving in the morning
before my parents wake up?
[♪ eerie music playing]
♪
[line ringing]
[Nora]
Alice. it's 3:00 a.m.
Hey. uh. sorry to call so late.
I was thinking we could go to Hunts Point.
show the picture around?
[♪ mellow music playing]
[liquid pouring]
-Ah.
-[car thumping]
-Jesus.
-Sorry.
You sleep as much as I do.
Who did that to your face?
[clicking tongue]
I don't wanna talk about it.
Who the fuck did that to your face?
A guy I met on the internet.
I asked him to.
Tell them not to leave a mark.
What?
You think I've never asked someone
to smack me around a little
in the throes of a passionate embrace?
[chuckles]
You think I've never let someone
take a few whacks at this piñata?
-[laughing]
-[laughing] A p... Mm-hmm.
[clearing throat]
Okay.
Why did the suspect
give us this picture?
What does she want us to do with it?
Come on. talk me through it.
game it out.
It puts the focus on Jay Easton
-and off her.
-Yep.
Or she's calling her shot.
telling us who's next.
Jay Easton's the only man
still alive in that picture.
Why would she want us
to know who's next?
Why would she want us to tell
Jay Easton that she's coming?
She wants him to be afraid
like she was afraid.
Yes.
She's doing to these men
what her trafficker did to her.
She's withholding food and water.
Traffickers control all aspects
of these girls' lives.
When they eat. what they wear.
when they get to sleep.
even where they sit in the car.
So. she's stuck.
-Keep talking.
-She's... she's stuck playing
and replaying the things
that happened to her.
but switching roles.
[Alice sighs]
But I don't know.
I mean. Jay Easton's dying.
I mean. when I went to his house.
he's on oxygen.
It's public knowledge.
She could have found that out.
decided she had to do this now.
Right?
If he dies of natural causes...
Oh. then she didn't get to kill him.
-She stays powerless.
-Mm-hmm.
Have you ever
come across Jay Easton before?
Has he been on your radar?
Rumors. you know.
And a man like that
isn't gonna get his hands dirty.
But you're right to be
asking questions about him.
Maybe we can find these girls
and get Jay Easton too.
[car engine turning off]
[Alice]
Why did you crop just their heads?
Jesus Christ. never show
anyone the whole picture
if you don't have to.
-Never give information away for free.
-Okay.
You're not a cop anymore.
When you get a new piece
of information on a case.
you sit on it.
you think about what it means.
why you have it.
and then you think some more.
I'm not joking around.
You go after someone
like Jay Easton.
you can't just wound him.
You wait to shoot
till the barrel is on his forehead.
Come on. you wanted to work all night.
Evening.
Don't be afraid. you're not in trouble.
I was wondering if you could
help us out. we're trying to...
[Alice] I'm just looking for this girl.
What about this guy?
You ever seen him?
[Nora] She could go
by the name Isabel Luna. Here.
[Alice] I'm looking for this girl.
Isabel.
It's an old picture.
She probably might not look
like this anymore. but...
Can you take another look.
-They're not familiar to you?
-[pimp] Hey!
Okay. well. thank you for your help.
Stay safe. take care.
You know none of that's
going to lead anywhere.
but you have to do it.
Brickwork on the street.
You're good at it.
Now you're supposed to say.
"Not as good as you. Nora."
-Not as good as you. Nora.
-Oh. thank you.
I mean it.
It's funny that
she's out there somewhere. right?
This woman.
This avenging angel.
this evil fury. our murderess.
She's out there right now
looking at the same sky we are.
Poetic.
Yeah. I'm about to start singing.
You're gonna have to hold me back.
-[gasps]
-Fuck no. let it out. let's go.
-♪ Have you seen her ♪
-Oh?
-♪ Tell me. have you seen her. seen her ♪
-Ooh!
-♪ Ohh ♪
-[laughing]
[♪ light jazz music playing]
[gasps]
[sighs] Oh. my God.
you scared me. [chuckles]
I'm sorry. [chuckles]
-Hi.
Are you Blanchard's... friend?
Yeah. Yeah.
Could I have some coffee?
-Sure.
-Is Blanchard's dad here. too?
Uh. no. he had an early morning.
-I actually do. too.
-I do. too.
Yeah. I actually have
a early morning work Zoom.
So. I was wondering
if I could get on your WiFi.
Um... sure.
Could you actually plug this in for me?
-[items clattering]
-[Catherine groaning]
And that coffee would be great.
Thank you.
[beeping]
-Anything?
-No.
If she was in any porn as a child.
her face would've come up.
You wanna be in this squad.
your reward is a code to that room.
That fucking room.
where we watch child pornography.
the darkest pit of Hades
down deep in the bowels of the Earth.
[Alice] So. you searched
all existing child pornography
in the database for her face?
Why is there never fucking coffee?
We have facial recognition software.
but we don't have fucking coffee beans.
So she's not in any pornography
and we didn't find her
on the streets last night.
So. where do we go next?
Aren't those for the kids?
Yeah. but I bought them.
so they're also mine.
So there's no records
on Isabel Luna after the age of 15?
No. nothing.
And she's not listed as missing.
-The records just stop.
-Yeah.
You have to actually go
to where she was living
-and talk to someone.
-I called her last placement.
It's a group home outside Albany.
I wanna go today.
Great. Brickwork.
Hey.
Go make me coffee.
-More brickwork?
-That's fucking right.
If there are no records after she's 15.
we should also take a look
at. uh. bodies. right?
Jane Does in the tri-state area
around 2012.
We could start a search
with what she was wearing that night.
The sequin dress. those bracelets.
One of 'em looks like
a hospital ID band.
[sighs]
[computer mouse clicking]
[Yara] Good morning!
-[Alice] Morning.
-[Yara] It's supposed to rain later.
I love when it rains. [chuckles]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Alice] You find anything?
-[Nora] Nope. not yet.
-[phone beeps]
[Alice] Hey. Choi just texted me.
Emma Easton just showed up
with her lawyer.
Why don't you take this one with Choi?
I'll work on the Jane Does.
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh-huh.
-Mom. don't...
-For sure. yeah.
-[mouthing] Go.
-[Catherine] Of course. yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey. um...
Yeah. I agree. Janet.
I think that's the best way forward.
[whispering]
Sorry. this is really important.
No.
Janet. I think you're on mute.
Yeah.
A deal is a deal. Janet.
Can you please let Mike say something?
Five.
Yeah. five.
[indistinct chatter]
Morning.
-What happened to your face?
-Hm?
Did that happen
after you left my house?
-[Frank] Hey. guys.
-What are you doing?
[Frank] Okay. Emma Easton
and her lawyer are here
because Danny called and said
we have info we want to share.
I'm doing my job. alright?
We have a picture of her dad
and two victims.
and we need to see
if she can identify the girl and...
[Frank] What happened to you?
What's wrong with your face?
What happened to you?
It's nothing.
-Okay. w-what is going on here?
-I'm fine.
Nora and I showed the pictures
around on the street
and we've been searching databases.
I got a hit
on a foster care placement.
Danny and I can head out there today.
And what do we do
about this. uh. Emma Easton interview?
-How do we play it?
-We show her the picture.
Of an underage hooker
sitting on her daddy's lap?
No. we're not doing that.
We're the FBI.
We play chess. not checkers.
-No offense. buddy.
-No. no offense taken.
I like tic-tac-toe. so...
So we tease we have something.
see if she wants to talk.
Fine. lay the groundwork.
do a little mindfuck on her.
Take it nice and gentle.
put her in the slow cooker.
You wanna do a mindfuck.
you should have Alice talk.
-No one better.
-Oh. I learned from the best.
Send me and Danny in.
pretend you're running late.
We'll play sweet and dumb.
[Danny]
What the fuck is going on?
[Alice] Nothing.
It wasn't him. okay?
I don't wanna talk about it.
[♪ tense music playing]
-Hey. Yara?
-[Yara] Yeah?
Any chance you signed up
for that mental health thing
Ed George is heading up?
Of course. I did.
I'm all about mental health.
If it's not too late.
can you sign me up. too?
Yeah. of course.
Great! Great!
[assistant] Hey. Ed?
There's a request
to add Nora Washington
to the seminar today.
Shall I add her to the list?
[Alice]
Uh. wow. yeah. this is embarrassing.
Um. I'm so sorry.
I don't know where my boss is.
Do you think we could
get started without him?
-Well...
-It's fine. Hal. I just wanna help.
So this is a courtesy conversation
because you said you had
some new information. so.
And Miss Easton's been
extremely generous and cooperative.
Well. thank you. Wow.
You know. that's really important to us.
And... and I... I just wanna say I'm sorry.
We got off on the wrong foot
the other day.
-I appreciate you saying that.
-[Alice] Good.
Okay. good.
We really just brought you here
because we're very concerned
about you.
We have new information
that's leading us to believe
that this person might be
targeting your family.
Oh. [chuckles]
What information?
I'm sorry. we... we can't tell you
at this time. but...
Oh.
Um. we just wanna make sure
that you're safe.
[Hal]
Well. thank you for your concern.
I'm not gonna lie.
she pisses me off.
-but she's good.
-[Danny] Have you noticed
anything out of the ordinary lately?
Any suspicious people
hanging around.
hang-up phone calls.
suspicious emails or texts?
-Mm-mm.
-[Danny] No?
-[Alice] Wow. okay.
-[Danny] Oh. okay. good. good.
Um. and... and your father. he...
Jay Easton's undergoing
treatment for cancer right now.
-I think you...
-We've been public about it.
We wanted to raise awareness
of glioblastoma.
-which is what my father has.
-Mm.
-Wow.
That is... that is...
wow. that's extraordinary.
-Mm-hmm.
-I. I don't wanna cause him undue stress.
but these investigations
can get invasive.
They can. very.
It's easier to point us
in the right direction.
because otherwise. pff...
we're just going
to have to look everywhere.
[scoffs]
Okay.
Well...
Here.
Call anytime.
You know... [scoffs] I'm just a cop.
but I really wanna show Miss Easton
the picture that we got.
of her dad with the girl.
What picture?
-[Alice] I don't think we can.
-[Danny] Oh. right.
Right. 'cause the girl
in the picture's a minor.
Oh. you shit sack.
fuckhead little cop.
Maybe just...
take a quick look.
[picture flapping lightly. sliding]
[pen tapping]
Do you know who this is?
Of course. I don't.
Do you have any idea how easy
it is to manipulate pictures?
My father
is an extraordinarily successful man
that's responsible for paying
millions of dollars in taxes.
We don't know a lot of your
father's financial details
'cause it's a private company.
[Hal] Well. this is not
a financial conversation. so.
-Yeah. but she brought it up.
-[Emma] What did you want to happen
when you showed me that picture?
Did you want me
to break down in tears
and tell you that my father
likes to go out with girls.
and it makes me sad?
That is not a real picture.
My brother is dead.
My father is undergoing
chemotherapy treatment.
If you wanna go after my family. go ahead.
I'm sure you will really benefit
from that decision.
[Hal]
Then this is done. Thank you.
[Frank sighs]
-Thanks for coming in.
-[Hal] Mm-mm.
-So she knows about Dad.
-Yeah. well. looks like it. Hm.
Did you wanna tell me
you were gonna show the picture?
You don't tell me anything anymore.
-[scoffs]
-Yeah.
Wow.
[whispering] I don't know. like.
maybe she doesn't have WiFi at her place.
No. I'm serous.
[whispering]
You just need to speak to her.
Okay. I've gotta go. you've gotta go.
I can't be here with her in my house.
-[continues whispering indistinctly]
-I... I'll take care of it. okay?
Stay right there.
Um. so... [clearing throat]
Um... my mom has gotta go to work
and. uh. I also have to take off. so...
I think I'm gonna take a shower.
No. uh...
[scoffs]
You have to go. I'm sorry.
-I just want a shower.
-You can shower in your own home.
What are you gonna do if I don't leave?
Are you serious?
Oh. okay. uh. things... things feel
a little. uh. hostile right now.
-What... what just happened?
-Are you gonna call the police?
-Yeah. we might. sure.
-We're not gonna... Mom?
We're not gonna call the police.
are you crazy?
-I'll call them right now.
-Mom. Mom. Mom. no. no. no. no. no.
-We can't. we can't.
-[scoffs] Why?
No. no. we can't call the police.
She's a sex worker.
What?
-Christ. Blanchard!
-Hey. hey. whoa. whoa. whoa.
Former. former.
She's a former sex worker.
-She does advocacy now.
-Did you pay her?
No. former!
-[Raquel sighs]
-What does former mean to you?
-How did you meet?
-She messaged me through an app.
Oh. my God.
Mom. Mom. Mom.
just please don't... don't call...
don't call the police.
because if you call the police.
then this becomes public.
Which. I mean. do you think
that's the best idea?
No. I'm just... I'm just saying.
maybe... maybe we could...
maybe we could call... call Dad.
Call Dad.
-Yeah. call Dad.
-[Raquel exhales sharply]
Go. Go away.
I don't wanna see you right now.
-Somewhere I can't see you!
-Sorry.
[line ringing]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Raquel sighs deeply]
[door opens. closes]
-Honey?
-[Hal] Raquel?
[Raquel] We're in the living room.
[footsteps approaching]
I'm here. what's going on?
What?
This is insane.
I don't know what to do.
Hi.
I'm Marta.
[phone dings]
[Danny] Is that Nora?
Has she had any luck
searching the Jane Does?
No.
What?
Just... just say it.
What do you wanna say to me?
Would you just tell me
who did that to you?
Why. what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna drive to his house
-and beat him up?
-Okay. never mind. what the fuck?
It was a guy from the internet.
I'm on an app. it...
It was a guy who came over. and...
What?
-He beat you up?
-I asked him to.
I like it.
Get off on it.
I called you.
You didn't pick up. so...
Oh. is that why?
[sighs]
I was out.
I went to see Liam.
-At your old place?
-And you know what?
Maybe there's some things that
we just don't need to talk about. okay?
-Are you gonna talk to her?
-Yes. I'm gonna handle it.
-She's a sex worker.
-Former. former.
-Mom. former.
-Is that what she told you?
-Well. what do you think. she's lying?
-He met her on the internet.
-She could be anyone.
-Fuck that. Mom.
How am I supposed
to meet people otherwise. huh?
[Raquel] Why don't you get your own
apartment and do whatever you want?
-You asked me to move in so I can save...
-Come on. come on. come on.
Why don't you both leave
and I'll talk to her. okay?
Okay. Dad. I'm... I'm so sorry.
-Did you have sex with her?
-Of course. he did.
He'd stick his dick in a watermelon
if I left it on the table.
I am bisexual. Mom.
and that is insane to say.
-[scoffs]
-Hey. hey. Did you wear a condom?
-Oh. God.
-What? People don't wear
-condoms anymore. so...
-What?!
-I... I didn't cum. so I'm fine...
-Oh. my God!
-Mom. Mom. don't...
-Alright. alright. Raquel.
Raquel. please. just go. okay?
I'll handle it.
So. you have to get out of my house.
-You know who I am.
-I have no idea who you are.
You haven't called the police.
You haven't called the police
'cause they'll ask you questions.
Yeah. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Get out of my house right now.
-Okay.
-Good.
But you go with me.
[Hal sighs]
So. you can tell your family...
you're heading back to work...
and then walk me down.
Or...
I'll tell them how we know each other.
[sighs]
[Hal sighs deeply]
[Hal]
You stay away from my family.
Okay. Sounds good.
Where'd you get that picture?
Of Jay Easton and the girl?
[Hal sighs]
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
And you are gonna end up dead.
[whispering]
I don't care if I die.
[Hal gasps]
What the f...
[elevator dings]
[Catherine grunting]
[car alarm chirping]
[car engine starting]
[car doors closing]
[Danny] Oh. shit.
I got one bar.
I hate it upstate.
Smells like rocks.
[scoffs] You need a cigarette.
-I'm fine.
-[Jolie] Agents. there you are.
Hello.
This way.
Oh. here we are.
my home away from home.
[Alice] Thank you
for seeing us. Miss Dixon.
Ah. it's Jolie.
And careful driving home.
There's a flash flood warning
and it comes on quick out here.
We'll be careful.
So. how long have you
been running this place?
Uh. 25 years in August.
I was a pediatric nurse.
I came here to give
career training seminars
to the girls and never left.
You know what. a lot of the girls
have gone on to become nurses.
I was in a place like this
when I was a kid.
It saved my life.
[Jolie chuckles softly]
Alright. this is what I have
on Isabel Luna.
She was placed with us
a few different times.
Oh. I encourage the girls
to save the things they're proud of.
and I put 'em all together
in a little memory box
and give it to them.
But she took off
before I could give it to her.
[Danny] Took off?
What does that mean?
She ran away a couple times.
[Alice] Danny?
Adrian.
You remember Adrian's last name?
No idea.
Boyfriend. I think?
She was a tough girl.
Kind of a leader.
not always in a good way.
But she loved to draw.
All those girly things.
Hearts and flowers.
But honestly.
the last time she ran away...
I thought there was a chance
she was pregnant.
-At 14?
-She didn't want to talk about it.
Do you happen to have
the names of the girls
who were here
at the same time as Isabel?
Well. she just ran away?
I thought she'd come back.
[Danny]
You're supposed to take care of kids
and you let a pregnant 14-year-old girl
staying here under your care
just run away?
-Uh...
-I have 20 girls who don't wanna be here.
I'll take any ideas you have
on how to make that work.
It's just that one of the girls
who was here with Isabel
could be involved
with multiple homicides.
Did Isabel have any close friends?
Catherine Grace.
Okay.
C? K?
[Jolie] C.
Catherine did whatever Isabel did.
Isabel protected her
from the other girls.
They bullied her. you know?
Because...
she was sort of strange.
Strange?
-How?
-Well. the way she'd look at people.
She'd stare.
Catherine got placed
in a home with a family.
and I swear she started acting out
so they'd send her back here.
To be with Isabel?
[Alice]
Nora. we're on our way back.
We're trying to get more
information about a girl.
Catherine Grace.
Ask how she's doing on the Jane Does.
if she's gonna call someone.
It's a voicemail. Danny.
-[truck honking]
-Shit! Fuck.
-Pull over.
-Where? I can't even see.
[host] And to get us started.
the assistant special agent
of New York. Ed George.
-[applause]
-Ed?
Hey. everyone.
thanks for coming today.
-Even though you had to.
-[light laughter]
Look. I think for too long
we've been promoting
this stereotype
of what a Fed is supposed to be.
Strong and silent.
But the truth is. we're human
and this job
requires a lot of sacrifice.
And I think it's important
that we. as an agency.
start making some space
to talk about that.
-[Nora] Mm.
-And...
I'm proud to help
start that conversation.
[applause]
Okay. we've got some folks from EAP
that are gonna lead us today.
[clapping] Let's get into it.
-Thank you. [chuckles]
-[Ed] Yeah.
[Cynthia] Thank you
for that lovely introduction. Ed.
[Danny] Christ. could you chew
with your mouth closed?
[bag crinkling]
Alright. stop it.
It got worse.
I'm breathing through my nose.
I don't know. it got worse.
Were you lying to that lady
about how you grew up
in a home like that?
Was that a lie?
You said...
when I took you home
from Amy's party.
you said that I didn't ask you
about what was going on with you
because I didn't wanna know.
Al.
I wanna know.
Yes.
For a few months
when I was 14. I ran away.
My dad wouldn't let me
come back home.
Why?
Because I...
I was in love with someone and...
I actually don't wanna
talk about it. okay?
We put Liam in a home.
A place like back there.
He's big now.
and he was getting pretty tough. so I...
I went to see him last night.
Oh.
Is that what you want?
Uh. what?
Your face.
someone hurting you like that?
-[chuckles] Wow.
-No. seriously.
I mean. I... I don't get it.
Could you just explain it to me?
No. not really.
No. seriously.
I'm not trying to be a dick.
-Oh.
-Just. I don't get it.
I don't give a shit
how you feel about it.
Believe me. I know.
Does it make you happy?
Yeah.
When it's happening. yeah.
Good. look. and... and I want you
to be happy.
Fuck that.
You want me to be happy
if it makes sense to you.
This is who I am right now.
And I don't need you to tell me
I'm amazing and try to save me.
I don't want you
to keep fucking saving me.
You think I like this?
You know. you think I like
feeling the way I feel about you?
It's a fucking nightmare.
A black fucking hole.
What do you feel about me?
I gotta smoke.
You're smoking a lot.
Yeah. well. you know.
you want me to smoke outside?
-I'll fucking smoke outside.
-I didn't say go outside.
-Fuck it. I'll go outside.
-Why would I say go outside?
That's so stupid.
-You can't light that out here!
-[lighter flicking]
This is so stupid!
-What?
-This is so stupid!
What?
[laughing]
What are you doing?
What are we doing?
This is so stupid.
[chuckles]
[panting]
[laughing]
[Hal muttering]
[continues laughing]
[exhales sharply. continues laughing]
PTSD can be a wild ride.
The smell. touch. taste. sound.
It can bring you right back
into that stressful memory.
And if anything here rings any bells.
please let us know.
And what about anger?
Yes. anger can be a form of PTSD.
Did you know in ancient times...
sorry. I'm a nut about mythology.
-[chuckles]
-But did you know in ancient times.
the Greeks saw anger
as a kind of insanity?
Uh. no. I didn't know that.
[chuckles]
There were different kinds of anger.
There's menis.
the anger of a society.
the anger of a people.
And there's thumos.
the anger that makes you fight.
that makes you kill.
that makes you a hero.
And then there's orge.
That's the slow. quiet anger
that builds up in you
until you finally decide
to do something about it.
But all of them can make you insane.
according to the Greeks.
Orge. uh. okay.
Thank you for that history lesson.
Is this a good time for a break?
Alright. let's take ten. everybody.
[claps]
Where are you headed?
I'll walk you there.
Outside. fresh air.
-It's supposed to start raining later.
-Great. perfect.
What a cool thing you're doing.
This is why you keep
moving up through the ranks.
What a great idea.
I wish I'd had it
when you were my supervisor.
You told me to. mm. suck it up
and eat it. right?
Well. technically.
I still am your supervisor.
But we're all evolving.
And. yeah.
Yeah. that's how I was taught.
And that's why we have
to break the cycle.
Oh. I like that.
Break the cycle.
Oh. I meant to tell you.
You remember
that police cooperation
we were doing
on Jay Easton's son's homicide?
[clicking tongue] I think so.
Well. it might be tied to this cold case.
An overdose from 2012.
A 15-year-old girl found dead in a river.
Do you remember that?
-No.
-Oh.
Because there might be questions.
It's both our names on it.
I just thought you should know. Ed.
[elevator dings]
Mind if I ride with you?
Just headed down to the basement
where they keep me.
Yeah. that's great.
I haven't had a chance to talk to you
since that supervisor drinks thing.
And we didn't get to talk
too much that night either.
You were hitting it pretty hard.
You know. the wellness
and resiliency program
I've been heading up
has an open door policy
for agents with alcohol
and substance problems.
If you ever have any questions...
Wasn't Dionysus the god of drink?
You ever read about him?
-[elevator dings]
-Alright. talk soon.
[elevator dings]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Hi.
Hey. I'm Detective Marshall Connelly.
-I'm working under...
-I know who you are.
Okay. good.
Yeah. I was wondering if I could. uh.
just steal a moment of your time.
Yeah. yeah. give me a minute.
Okay.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
Fuck.
Alden. I'm back.
Beauty. where are you?
I don't know how to tell you this.
Uh. what's going on?
I don't wanna keep any more secrets.
I have feelings for you.
And I want you to be my girlfriend.
[footsteps approaching]
-[♪ romantic music playing on phone]
-It's romantic.
-He loves you.
-♪ The self-esteem to match ♪
-I love you.
-♪ What a catch ♪
♪ What a catch ♪
I can feel my fingers.
What? What did she say?
Say yes.
-♪ You'll never catch us ♪
-Okay.
♪ So just let me be ♪
Yes.
[chuckles] Yes.
[laughing]
Give me those.
[sniffling]
♪ Miss Flack.
said I still want you back ♪
-[thunder rumbling]
-♪ Yeah ♪
[Danny] See if you can find
any more information
on Catherine in the FBI database.
and I'll call Choi.
[keyboard clacking]
[Alice] Hey. she said she...
Hey. Jolie said she was training 'em
to be nurses. right?
Maybe Catherine
has medical experience.
Maybe she's working off the books.
How did you know
what I was gonna say?
[laughing] God...
-Hey. Choi. it's Danny.
-[phone ringing]
Listen. Jolie said she was
training the girls to be nurses.
Nora. hey. sorry.
I just got service back.
We got a ton of stuff on Isabel.
but I think we found the other girl. too.
Her name is Catherine Grace.
She was born in 1997
in Hoosick. New York.
Best friends with Isabel Luna.
The eyes are the same.
It's her.
Hey. Brickwork.
And guess what Isabel's
boyfriend's name was. hm?
Adrian.
Wow.
Murado. [chuckles]
That's great work.
Yep. and she might've had a child.
which could help
with the Jane Doe search.
I'm running it now.
Oh. shit.
Late February 2012.
Unidentified minor. overdose.
Signs of sexual activity.
possibly with a foreign object.
Given birth. no face left.
A floater off 95.
near the Byram River Bridge.
New York.
We'll go there.
[Nora] Actually. you're not
going to do anything more
with the Jane Doe.
Because when you're back. I'm taking you
off this for a little while.
[scoffs] Wait. what?
Marshall told me about an interaction
you had last night.
You talked to Marshall?
He claimed you showed up
to his house unannounced.
He says you were aggressive
and you took your gun out.
It was not unannounced. it was...
It's not an official complaint yet.
-Nora. you believe him?
-But the best thing
for your mental health
is to take a step back.
Why are you doing this?
It's a chance I never got
when I was in your shoes.
Just take a step back.
It was your case?
You don't get to question
a fucking thing that I do.
This is a paramilitary organization
and I'm the general.
I am so far above you.
you need a fucking telescope
to see me.
Send everything you have
on the home back to Choi
and get back here.
[♪ pensive music playing]
You okay?
[♪ "Have You Seen Her"
by The Chi-Lites playing]
♪ Oh. I hear her voice
as the cold winds blow ♪
♪ In the sweet music on my radio ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
-[coughing]
-♪ Why ♪
♪ Oh. why did she have to leave ♪
♪ And go away ♪
♪ Oh. I've been used ♪
♪ To having someone to lean on ♪
♪ And I'm lost ♪
♪ Baby. I'm lost ♪
♪ Whoa. bup-bup-bup.
bup-bup-bup ♪
♪ Bup-bup-bup. bup-bup-bup ♪
♪ Bup-bup-bup.
bup. bup. bup. bup ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
-♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
♪ Whoa. bup-bup-bup.
bup-bup-bup ♪
♪ Bup-bup-bup. bup-bup-bup ♪
♪ Bup-bup-bup.
bup. bup. bup. bup ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
-♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
♪ Oh. she left her kiss
upon my lips ♪
♪ But left that break
within my heart ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
♪ Oh. I see her hand
reaching out to me ♪
♪ Only she can set me free ♪
♪ Have you seen her ♪
♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
-♪ Tell me. have you seen her ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-